hey everyone today is thursday january
25th 2017 and i've been meaning to make
this video for a while
but you know the bible actually
prophesied about the mandela effect
yes it did and we're going to take a
look at those scripture verses today and
i will tell you that these scripture
verses that i'm going to show you
actually have been changed as well
but
praise the lord the essence is still
there and those of you who have eyes to
see and ears to hear will see the
changes now did you know that ice the
sea is no longer found in the new
testament
that's right our bibles are changing and
you need to wake up in jesus name
[Music]
daniel 7 25 says this today in the king
james bible and he shall speak great
words against the most high
and shall wear out the saints of the
most high
and think to change times and laws
this is about the antichrist
now i want to point out a few things to
you because this verse
has in fact been changed
i just want to point out a few things
here is that the title
of god
is most high
but now we see in daniel 7 25
the title they're giving him is high
do you see this high is capitalized but
most is not
and this is a great example of the type
of
gross
and blasphemous changes we're seeing in
the bible now
it's appalling
i want to point out a few things that
saints wasn't even mentioned
until the book of acts in the new
testament
but now we see it in the old testament
in the book of daniel
it was
by the way
and try
to wear out
the holy ones
not shall wear out the saints
the second thing i want to note it
wasn't
think to change times and laws it was
seek
to change times and laws there's a
difference in the wording
remember
8 11-12 we see the following behold the
days come saith the lord god that i will
send a famine in the land
not a famine of bread nor thirst for
water but of hearing the words
of the lord
and they shall wander from sea to sea
and from the north
even to the east
they shall run to and fro
to seek the word of the lord and shall
not find it
so a couple of things to note in amos 8
11 and 12
is in verse 11 it says hearing the words
of the lord plural
it was hearing the word of the lord
and you can see in verse 12 it still
retains the word of the lord
but then in verse 12 we see something
strange of wandering from the north even
to the east
how do you even do that
clearly that's been changed
but the essence remains
second thessalonians 2 8-11 we see a lot
of changes
but there is still truth to be grasped
here and then shall that wicked be
revealed whom the lord shall consume
with the spirit of his mouth and shall
destroy with the brightness of his
coming
even him whose coming is after the
working of satan with all power
and signs and lying wonders and with all
the siblings of unrighteousness in them
that perish
because they receive not the love of the
truth that they might be saved
and for this cause god shall send them
strong delusion that they
should believe
a lie
let's take a look at 2 thessalonians 2 8
because there are a couple of changes
here worth noting
and then shall that wicked
note that wicked is capitalized
now i remember the lawless one not
that wicked and then it goes on to say
that the lord shall consume
with the spirit of his mouth
i don't remember the lord ever consuming
with the spirit of his mouth it was
breath of his mouth
do you remember
in 2 thessalonians 2 9 we see all power
and signs and lying wonders it's been
changed it was lying signs and wonders
do you remember that lying signs and
wonders
and then in verse 10 it says something
really weird that
it was because they received not the
love of the truth that they might be
saved no wasn't receiving not the love
of the truth it was because they did not
love the truth
you don't receive the love of the truth
do you see how that's been changed do
you remember
in verse 11 it says and for this cause
god shall send them strong delusion it
wasn't in for this cause it was and for
this reason
god shall send them a strong delusion
they omitted the a
do you see that
and these are the types of changes we
see throughout the king james bible now
so many crazy changes
thousands of changes
in revelations 22 18 and 19 we see god
giving a prophecy and condemning
anyone who added to or removed
words of the prophecy
and this is what it says for i testify
unto every man that heareth the words of
the prophecy of this book if any man
shall add unto these things god shall
add unto him the plagues that are
written in this book and if any man
shall take away from the words of the
book of this prophecy god shall take
away his part out of the book of life
and are the holy city and from the
things which are written in this book
in second timothy 4 4
we read and they shall turn away their
ears from the truth and shall be turned
unto fables and this is exactly what's
happening right now as the bible's being
changed those who do not see the bible
changes for whatever reason are now
believing in fables
we learn in second peter 3 13 that in
last days there would be mockers
following after their own lusts well now
look what it reads knowing this first
that there shall come in the last days
scoffers walking after their own lusts
this verse has been changed
it wasn't scoffers it was mockers and
look how this verse is written now it's
really awkward
and then in verse 4 we see a grammar
mistake
you see the word coming and then a
question mark
and then the word for
and it starts with a lower cap letter
this is all throughout
the king james bible now
severe grammar issues
on every page
indicative
that the bible has in fact
been changed i know it's shocking but
it's undeniable
friends we need to remember that jesus
christ
is the king of kings the lord of lords
he is the living word of god no matter
what they do to our bibles they cannot
change the living word of god because
the word of god
is forever
and the bible is being changed but they
cannot change the eternal word of god
because it's forever and ever and ever
no matter what they do to our bibles
[Music]
you